DISUSULAIMON ABOLAJI

FRONTEND DEVELOPER || GRAPHIC DESIGNER

CONTACT

Address:

Block 33, flat 8, LKJ Gardens, Lasu-lba expressway, Igando, Lagos State

Phone:

07068417681, 08020551052

Email:

abolajiidiisu@gmail.com

SKILLS

Graphic skills

Photoshop CorelDraw Illustrator

Coding Skills

HTML CSS / SASS JavaScript React Git / GitHub

Soft Skills

Communication
Adaptability
Great work ethic
Problem solving
Teamwork

ABOUT ME

I am a passionate graphic and web designer with an interest with working with like-minded people in the tech and creative environments

I have 5+ years of experience in client work and solo projects as well as being a part of a work force

I have worked to extensively tight deadlines in multiple work environments; in the office, on events sites and printing warehouses

I have a **strong** understanding of the printing process and have built up rapports with printers whom I've worked with on multiple occasions

I enjoy working with peers and look forward to meeting new people in all prospective work environments

EXPERIENCE

Graphic	Designer
---------	----------

2016 to 2019

King Azeez Property

Work with the branding team to produce new ideas for company branding, promotional campaigns, and marketing communication

Cooperate with designers to create clean interfaces and simple, intuitive interactions and experiences.

Develop project concepts and maintain optimal workflow.

Work with senior developers to manage large, complex design projects for corporate clients.

Web Designer

2019 to 2021

CardsHub Nigeria

Evaluate trends, access new data and keep up-to-date with the latest marketing techniques

Design brochure, magazines and letterheads for corporate events

Direct brainstorming meetings and creative sessions
Create and implement tailored marketing plans

EDUCATION

SSCE 2007-2013

Lagos State Model College, Meiran

BSC

2015 - 2019

Botany, Lagos State University

LANGUAGES

English Advance
Yoruba Native
Arabic Intermediate